Subtitle Provide by dramacool.in Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.in [Admin.@YNG]
♪Passing by where leaves fall and flowers fade♪
♪المرور حيث تتساقط الأوراق وتذبل الزهور♪
♪Chancing upon shooting stars and northern lights♪
♪الصدفة على النجوم المتساقطة والأضواء الشمالية♪
♪At this moment, I borrow the wind♪
♪في هذه اللحظة، أستعير الريح♪
♪To set sail for distant seas♪
♪للإبحار إلى البحار البعيدة♪
♪Rumors swirl close to my ears♪
♪تدور الشائعات بالقرب من أذني♪
♪Some laugh and say my dreams are wild♪
♪يضحك البعض ويقولون أن أحلامي جامحة♪
♪Yet I will not change my original aspiration♪
♪ولكنني لن أغير طموحاتي الأصلية♪
♪Even if it means running into a wall♪
♪حتى لو كان ذلك يعني الاصطدام بالحائط♪
♪I know the road to growing up brings pain♪
♪أعلم أن الطريق إلى النمو يجلب الألم♪
♪Still, I hold fast to the dream I cherish♪
♪ما زلت متمسكًا بالحلم الذي أعتز به♪
♪Never have I thought to yield♪
♪لم أفكر أبدًا في الاستسلام♪
♪Youth is meant to stand against the world♪
♪الشباب هو من المفترض أن يقف في وجه العالم♪
♪I've always longed♪
♪لقد تمنيتها دائما♪
♪To stand upon the highest peak♪
♪الوقوف على أعلى قمة♪
♪I've always wished♪
♪لقد تمنيت دائما♪
♪To cross a river wide and deep♪
♪لأعبر نهرًا واسعًا وعميقًا♪
♪In darkness, look up to see the sky turn clear♪
♪في الظلام، انظر إلى الأعلى لترى السماء تصبح صافية♪
♪Unyielding♪
♪لا يلين♪
♪The butterfly reborn from its cocoon must fly♪
♪الفراشة المولودة من شرنقتها يجب أن تطير♪
♪Like bamboo breaking forth, I chase dreams through hardship♪
♪مثل الخيزران الذي ينبت، أطارد الأحلام من خلال المشقة♪
♪Return to me, my dream♪
♪ارجع إليّ يا حلمي♪
♪Unyielding♪
♪لا يلين♪
♪My pure heart stays the same♪
♪قلبي النقي يبقى كما هو♪
♪You must face the wind♪
♪يجب عليك مواجهة الريح♪
♪And go where your heart leads♪
♪واذهب إلى حيث يقودك قلبك♪
♪Embrace the moonlight that belongs to you♪
♪احتضن ضوء القمر الذي ينتمي إليك♪
♪In the dark♪
♪في الظلام♪
=Voyage to Haihun, Season 1=
=رحلة إلى هايهون، الموسم الأول=
=Episode 13=
=الحلقة 13=
Why does your blade look
لماذا يبدو النصل الخاص بك
exactly the same as mine?
نفس الشيء تمامًا مثل لي؟
They were forged as a pair.
لقد تم تشكيلهم كزوج.
Weapons passed down from my sect.
الأسلحة التي انتقلت من طائفتي.
Your name is De Jiu?
اسمك دي جيو؟
And your master is Yun Qing, the Swift Blade?
وسيدك هو يون تشينغ، السيف السريع؟
Though we are wandering heroes,
على الرغم من أننا أبطال متجولون،
our skills often go unused.
في كثير من الأحيان لا يتم استخدام مهاراتنا.
At most, we smooth over disputes
على الأكثر، نحن نحل النزاعات
just to make a living.
فقط لكسب لقمة العيش.
Your master was a man of burning passion
كان سيدك رجلاً ملتهب العاطفة
and determined to clear the name of wandering heroes.
وعزم على تطهير اسم الأبطال المتجولين.
So, he took on tasks for the court.
فتولى مهام المحكمة.
Over time, he stopped returning to the village.
مع مرور الوقت، توقف عن العودة إلى القرية.
Though Master raised me from childhood,
على الرغم من أن المعلم رباني منذ الطفولة،
I never truly understood him.
لم أفهمه حقًا أبدًا.
But his letters and his heart
لكن رسائله وقلبه
were mostly filled with you.
كانت مليئة بك في الغالب.
Then, in your eyes,
ثم في عينيك،
what kind of man was he?
أي نوع من الرجل كان؟
Stern and seldom smiling,
صارم ونادرًا ما يبتسم،
unusually strict.
صارمة بشكل غير عادي.
Every word he spoke carried reason.
كل كلمة قالها كانت تحمل معنى.
When I slacked off,
عندما كنت متراخيا،
he never scolded me.
لم يوبخني أبدًا.
But no matter how well I did,
ولكن بغض النظر عن مدى نجاحي،
he never once praised me.
لم يمدحني قط.
You were always in his heart.
لقد كنت دائما في قلبه.
In his view,
في رأيه،
you were not his disciple anymore.
لم تعد تلميذه بعد الآن.
You were his daughter.
لقد كنت ابنته.
He was a close friend of your birth father.
لقد كان صديقًا مقربًا لأبيك البيولوجي.
That day, he heard your family was in danger.
في ذلك اليوم سمع أن عائلتك في خطر.
But by the time he arrived, it was too late.
ولكن عندما وصل كان الوقت قد فات.
Just as the villains were about to harm you,
كما كان الأشرار على وشك أن يؤذوك،
he fought with all he had to keep you safe.
لقد حارب بكل ما لديه ليحافظ على سلامتك.
Though badly wounded,
على الرغم من إصابته بجروح بالغة،
seeing you unharmed
رؤيتك سالما
and crying in his arms,
وتبكي بين ذراعيه،
he felt it was all worth it.
لقد شعر أن الأمر يستحق كل هذا العناء.
From that day on,
ومن ذلك اليوم فصاعدا،
he took any job that could earn money.
لقد قبل أي عمل يمكنه من كسب المال.
No matter how dangerous,
بغض النظر عن مدى خطورة ذلك،
all he wanted was to give you a better life.
كل ما أراده هو أن يمنحك حياة أفضل.
So, he became a spy for the court,
فأصبح جاسوسا للمحكمة،
even if it meant danger, toil,
حتى لو كان ذلك يعني الخطر والتعب،
and disdain.
والازدراء.
Firstly, it was to atone for your parents.
أولاً، كان ذلك للتكفير عن والديك.
Secondly, for you, he had no regrets.
ثانياً، بالنسبة لك، لم يكن لديه أي ندم.
Master once said
قال المعلم ذات مرة
that once a person holds onto a wish,
أنه بمجرد أن يتمسك الشخص بأمنية،
the blade will lose its sharpness.
سوف تفقد الشفرة حدتها.
You are
أنت
what he's been holding onto.
ما كان متمسكا به.
Uncle, your blade's aura
عمي هالة شفرتك
made me feel the warmth of someone I once knew.
جعلني أشعر بدفء شخص كنت أعرفه ذات يوم.
But I will never
ولكنني لن افعل ذلك ابدًا
see him again.
رؤيته مرة أخرى.
(Wucheng Village)
(قرية ووتشنغ)
- Duke. - Can you two vanish?
- دوق. - هل يمكنكم الاختفاء؟
Lord Li Han has ordered
لقد أمر اللورد لي هان
that we ensure your safety.
أننا نضمن سلامتك.
Duke,
دوق،
the closer we get to Chang'an, the more cautious we must be.
كلما اقتربنا من تشانغآن، يجب علينا أن نكون أكثر حذرا.
Can you two lend a hand?
هل يمكنكم تقديم يد المساعدة؟
Carry those things back.
أحمل تلك الأشياء مرة أخرى.
Quickly, quickly.
بسرعة، بسرعة.
Careful now.
كن حذرا الآن.
Put some strength into it.
ضع بعض القوة فيه.
Mr. and Mrs. Kang have arrived.
لقد وصل السيد والسيدة كانغ.
Please serve the tea.
من فضلك قدم الشاي.
Mr. Kang.
السيد كانغ.
My apologies.
اعتذاري.
The venue is booked for today.
تم حجز المكان لهذا اليوم.
Don't stop them.
لا توقفهم.
Let them come through.
دعهم يأتون.
The more people, the livelier.
كلما زاد عدد الأشخاص، كلما أصبحنا أكثر حيوية.
I am Kang Ning.
انا كانغ نينغ.
Nice to meet you.
سعيد بلقائك.
I am Qi Chang.
أنا تشي تشانغ.
- Please.
- من فضلك.
Your lady's grace feels familiar.
نعمة سيدتك تشعر بأنها مألوفة.
Have we met in Changyi?
هل التقينا في تشانغيي؟
You're from Changyi as well?
هل أنت من تشانغيي أيضًا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Last time, I returned to visit my family.
في المرة الأخيرة، عدت لزيارة عائلتي.
I saw the equine administration thriving in Changyi.
لقد رأيت إدارة الخيول مزدهرة في تشانغي.
So, I joined in.
لذا انضممت.
So, you are Xu Pingjun,
إذًا، أنت شو بينجون،
who broke the wood?
من كسر الخشب؟
Xu Pingjun,
شو بينجون,
the Geng contestant.
المتسابق جينج.
Meeting an old friend in a foreign land is truly a blessing.
إن لقاء صديق قديم في بلد أجنبي هو نعمة حقيقية.
I never expected Qi
لم أتوقع تشي أبدًا
to have the chance to meet my lady.
أن أحصل على فرصة مقابلة سيدتي.
That is quite the fated bond.
إنها رابطة مصيرية تماما.
- Come.
- تعال.
Your attire tells me
ملابسك تخبرني
you must be a wandering hero.
لا بد أنك بطل متجول.
Has this sword
هل هذا السيف
ever tasted blood?
هل سبق لك أن تذوقت الدم؟
A wandering hero may break the law by force,
قد يخرق البطل المتجول القانون بالقوة،
but he would never take a life lightly.
ولكنه لن يأخذ الحياة باستخفاف أبدًا.
To abstain is to endure,
الامتناع هو التحمل
but that does not mean never to kill.
ولكن هذا لا يعني عدم القتل أبدًا.
There are times when one has no choice.
هناك أوقات لا يكون فيها أمامنا خيار.
Seems you also hold the heart of a wandering hero.
يبدو أنك تحمل أيضًا قلب البطل المتجول.
Of course.
بالطبع.
With the sky as my canopy,
مع السماء كمظلتي،
the earth as my seat,
الأرض مقعدي،
elegant melodies all around...
ألحان أنيقة في كل مكان...
Kindred spirits by our side...
أرواح متقاربة بجانبنا...
We drink and share our joy.
نشرب ونشارك فرحتنا.
Unbound by the ways of the world.
غير مقيد بطرق العالم.
How carefree and at ease it feels.
كم أشعر بالراحة والطمأنينة.
Ha ha ha.
هاهاهاها.
- Come.
- تعال.
Yet,
حتى الآن،
fate toys with us.
القدر يلعب بنا
True chivalry lies not in appearance,
"إن الفروسية الحقيقية لا تكمن في المظهر،
but in the heart.
ولكن في القلب.
Chivalry of the court
فروسية المحكمة
lies in the affairs of the realm.
يكمن في شؤون المملكة.
To bring the people a good life
لتوفير حياة جيدة للناس
is the path of chivalry.
هو طريق الفروسية.
Chivalry of the common folks
فروسية عامة الناس
lies in the care for right and wrong.
تكمن في الاهتمام بالصواب والخطأ.
Welding the swords
لحام السيوف
is for the sake
من أجل ذلك
of justice.
من العدالة.
Mr. Kang.
السيد كانغ.
A wise insight.
بصيرة حكيمة.
You're dressed so elegantly.
أنت ترتدي ملابس أنيقة جداً.
You must be a noble headed for Chang'an.
لا بد وأنك شخص نبيل متجه إلى تشانغآن.
I only hope you'll bring blessings to the people.
أتمنى فقط أن تجلب البركات للناس.
Then the wandering heroes like us
ثم الأبطال المتجولين مثلنا
can retire from the martial world.
يمكنه التقاعد من عالم القتال.
You jest.
انت هو.
Whether in the court or among the people,
سواء في المحكمة أو بين الناس،
our hearts are always with the people's well-being.
قلوبنا دائما مع مصلحة الشعب.
To bring peace to a land,
لإحلال السلام في الأرض،
or to save just one or a few lives,
أو لإنقاذ حياة واحدة أو عدد قليل من الأرواح،
is all part of the path of chivalry.
كل هذا جزء من طريق الفروسية.
Today,
اليوم،
meeting you feels like reuniting with an old friend.
إن اللقاء بك يشعرني وكأنني التقيت بصديق قديم.
I will offer tea in place of wine.
سأقدم الشاي بدلًا من النبيذ.
An honor to meet you, Qi.
شرف لي أن أقابلك، تشي.
- Cheers.
- هتاف.
Who said you could peek?
من قال أنك تستطيع أن تنظر؟
Don't flatter yourself.
لا تبالغ في مدح نفسك.
I was merely passing by.
لقد كنت مجرد أمر.
But back in Hongnong,
ولكن بالعودة إلى هونغ نونغ،
you risked your life for me,
لقد خاطرت بحياتك من أجلي،
helping me clear my name.
مساعدتي في تبرئة اسمي.
I should thank you properly.
ينبغي لي أن أشكرك بشكل صحيح.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Don't get the wrong idea.
لا تفهم الفكرة الخاطئة.
It just seemed suspicious,
لقد بدا الأمر مشبوهًا،
so I happened to dig into Li Wei's affair.
لذا حدث أنني بحثت في قضية لي وي.
Your blade technique is impressive.
تقنية الشفرة الخاصة بك مثيرة للإعجاب.
Can you teach me a few moves for self-defense?
هل يمكنك أن تعلميني بعض الحركات للدفاع عن النفس؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Let's see what you can do first.
دعونا نرى ما يمكنك فعله أولاً.
Are you a monkey? All you do is run.
هل أنت قرد؟ كل ما تفعله هو الجري.
I can't beat you,
لا أستطيع التغلب عليك
so I have to run.
لذلك يجب علي أن أركض.
Still, you've got some good moves.
لا يزال لديك بعض التحركات الجيدة.
Want to learn? I can teach you.
هل تريد أن تتعلم؟ يمكنني أن أعلمك.
This is called parkour.
هذا ما يسمى بالباركور.
If you follow my method
إذا اتبعت طريقتي
and build up your core strength training,
وبناء تدريب القوة الأساسية لديك،
you can pick up parkour quickly.
يمكنك تعلم رياضة الباركور بسرعة.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Missing your master?
هل تفتقد سيدك؟
♪Alioth hangs low♪
♪Alioth يتدلى منخفضًا♪
♪Sinking into the night♪
♪الغرق في الليل♪
I heard from my master
سمعت من سيدي
that once a person harbors a thought,
أن الشخص بمجرد أن يؤمن بفكرة،
feelings soon follow.
وسوف تتبع ذلك المشاعر قريبا.
♪Paper gently sways♪
♪الورق يتأرجح بلطف♪
And when feelings take root,
وعندما تتجذر المشاعر،
the blade loses its sharpness.
تفقد الشفرة حدتها.
♪Was last night peaceful♪
♪كانت الليلة الماضية هادئة♪
Go on, eat slowly.
إستمر، تناول الطعام ببطء.
I'll teach you the rapid mastery method
سأعلمك طريقة الإتقان السريع
of parkour as you eat.
من الباركور كما تأكل.
Parkour
باركور
is not just about the burst of strength when climbing,
لا يتعلق الأمر فقط باندفاع القوة عند التسلق،
but the release of force on landing.
ولكن إطلاق القوة عند الهبوط.
That's how you protect yourself.
هكذا تحمي نفسك.
Just look at you.
فقط أنظر إليك.
Moving stiffly up and down.
التحرك بشكل صارم إلى أعلى وإلى أسفل.
Your body rides on sheer momentum.
يعتمد جسدك على الزخم الهائل.
That's an easy way to get hurt.
هذه طريقة سهلة للإصابة.
♪Fragrance lingering in the sleeves♪
♪العطر يعلق في الأكمام♪
♪The topic ferments♪
♪الموضوع يتخمر♪
♪Lingering on♪
♪البقاء على قيد الحياة♪
♪Words drift and waver in the wind♪
♪الكلمات تتجول وتتمايل في الريح♪
You're so much stronger than I am.
أنت أقوى مني بكثير.
I could never be like you.
لا أستطيع أن أكون مثلك أبدًا.
When I was little, my parents didn't care for me.
عندما كنت صغيراً، لم يهتم بي والداي.
It was my grandmother who raised me.
لقد كانت جدتي هي التي ربتني.
She kept a close watch on me.
لقد ظلت تراقبني عن كثب.
And I kept wanting to run away.
وظللت أريد الهروب.
But every time, she dragged me back.
لكن في كل مرة كانت تسحبني للخلف.
Scolding and punishment always followed.
وكان التوبيخ والعقاب يتبعان دائمًا.
So I told myself:
فقلت لنفسي:
I must grow up quickly
يجب أن أكبر بسرعة
and leave her.
واتركها.
Later on,
في وقت لاحق،
Grandmother passed away.
توفيت الجدة.
It was then that I realized
حينها أدركت
just how much I couldn't bear to part with her.
كم لم أستطع أن أتحمل فكرة الانفصال عنها.
Someone told me
لقد أخبرني أحدهم
that I mustn't cry.
أنني لا يجب أن أبكي.
If I shed tears,
إذا ذرفت الدموع،
Grandmother wouldn't leave in peace.
الجدة لن تغادر بسلام.
So, I held it in,
لذا، احتفظت به في داخلي،
refusing to cry.
رفض البكاء
One day, I couldn't hold it back anymore
ذات يوم، لم أعد أستطيع التحمل أكثر من ذلك
and cried so hard.
وبكيت بشدة.
♪Between my lips and teeth♪
♪بين شفتي وأسناني♪
After the crying was over,
وبعد أن انتهى البكاء،
I drifted off to sleep again.
لقد غفوت مرة أخرى.
♪That confession♪
♪هذا الاعتراف♪
♪Hangs on the edge of the world♪
♪يعلق على حافة العالم♪
I had a dream.
لقد كان لدي حلم.
I dreamed of my grandmother
حلمت بجدتي
smiling as she bid me farewell.
ابتسمت وهي تودعني.
♪The stars pour across the sky♪
♪النجوم تتدفق عبر السماء♪
Heng.
هنغ.
♪Off to the ends of the world♪
♪إلى أقاصي العالم♪
- Heng. - What are you doing here?
-هنغ.- ماذا تفعل هنا؟
Senior.
كبير.
Why are you...?
لماذا انت...؟
What did you do to my senior?
ماذا فعلت لكباري؟
What could I possibly do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
I merely
انا فقط
treated her to a pastry
عالجتها بالمعجنات
and
و
chatted a bit about life with her.
تحدثت معها قليلا عن الحياة.
I saw it all.
لقد رأيت كل شيء.
What did you see?
ماذا رأيت؟
You...
أنت...
Well...
حسنًا...
Qi.
تشي.
I suppose
أفترض
this must be the Wang Heng you spoke of.
لا بد أن يكون هذا هو وانغ هينج الذي تحدثت عنه.
I am Wang Heng.
أنا وانغ هينغ.
Isn't this the young lady who broke the wood?
أليست هذه هي الفتاة التي كسرت الخشب؟
Nice to meet you, Wang Heng.
يسعدني أن ألتقي بك، وانغ هينغ.
Oh, you know each other.
أوه، أنتم تعرفون بعضكم البعض.
This is my new friend, Kang Ning.
هذا هو صديقي الجديد، كانغ نينغ.
A pleasure to meet you.
يسعدني أن أقابلك.
I was hoping to have a chat with Qi,
كنت أتمنى أن أتحدث مع تشي،
but I have matters to discuss with the Village Chief.
لكن لدي أمور أريد مناقشتها مع رئيس القرية.
Heng, Qi.
هنغ، تشي.
See you again.
أراك مرة أخرى.
- See you.
- أراك لاحقا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Kang Ning certainly carries himself with grace.
من المؤكد أن كانج نينج يحمل نفسه بنعمة.
Of course. He's my friend.
بالطبع. إنه صديقي.
What's going on between you and my senior?
ماذا يحدث بينك وبين كبيري؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Just be open about this.
فقط كن منفتحا بشأن هذا الأمر.
No need to hide it.
لا داعي لإخفائه.
Hide what?
إخفاء ماذا؟
Listen.
يستمع.
If a young lady doesn't like you,
إذا كانت الفتاة لا تحبك،
why would she risk her own safety for you?
لماذا تخاطر بسلامتها من أجلك؟
Back in Hongnong, when you were falsely accused,
في هونغ نونغ، عندما تم اتهامك زوراً،
my senior helped you investigate at once.
لقد ساعدك كبيري في التحقيق على الفور.
Could it be there's some spark between you two?
هل يمكن أن يكون هناك شرارة بينكما؟
No, absolutely not.
لا، بالتأكيد لا.
Let me make this clear.
دعني أوضح هذا.
She is my senior.
إنها أكبر مني.
Any matters of her feelings go through me first.
أي أمر يتعلق بمشاعرها يمر بي أولاً.
Shouldn't you
ألا ينبغي لك؟
show some stance?
إظهار بعض الموقف؟
Aren't you short on money?
هل أنت تعاني من نقص في المال؟
If your senior and I end up together,
إذا انتهى بي الأمر مع كبيرك في السن،
shouldn't you show some courtesy to your future brother-in-law?
ألا يجب عليك إظهار بعض المجاملة تجاه صهرك المستقبلي؟
Let's keep our affairs separate.
دعونا نبقي شؤوننا منفصلة.
Tsk, stingy.
تسك، بخيل.
(Wucheng Village)
(قرية ووتشنغ)
(Bashang Lodge, Bashang)
(نزل باشانغ، باشانغ)
(Bashang Post Station)
(محطة بريد باشانغ)
Everyone, listen up.
الجميع، استمعوا.
Wei Xian, Grand Herald,
وي شيان، كبير المبشرين،
will be coming to welcome us early tomorrow morning.
سيأتي للترحيب بنا في وقت مبكر من صباح الغد.
Make sure to rest early tonight.
تأكد من الراحة مبكرًا الليلة.
Do we have any special game here?
هل لدينا أي لعبة خاصة هنا؟
Duke.
دوق.
We're close to Chang'an.
نحن قريبون من تشانغآن.
You must watch your words and actions.
يجب عليك مراقبة أقوالك وأفعالك.
Don't stir up trouble again.
لا تثير المشاكل مرة أخرى.
Rest assured, Lord Gong.
اطمئن يا سيد غونغ.
I'll keep an eye on him.
سأبقي عينى عليه.
- Hey. - Let's go.
- مهلا. - دعنا نذهب.
Lord Li.
اللورد لي.
What's the matter so late at night?
ما الأمر في هذا الوقت المتأخر من الليل؟
Lord Wang.
اللورد وانغ.
There's a lord who wishes to meet you.
هناك سيد يرغب في مقابلتك.
Who might that be?
من قد يكون هذا؟
You'll know when you get there.
ستعرف عندما تصل إلى هناك.
This way, Lord Wang.
من هنا، يا سيد وانغ.
Was it you who sent for me?
هل أنت الذي أرسلت في طلبي؟
Shh.
ششش.
It's late.
إنه متأخر.
I didn't expect you to still have such refined taste.
لم أتوقع أن يكون لديك هذا الذوق الرفيع.
In old age, sleep comes lightly.
في الشيخوخة، يأتي النوم خفيفًا.
I'm just fishing
أنا فقط أمارس الصيد
for a bit of pleasure.
من أجل القليل من المتعة.
It seems you've had
يبدو أنك قد حصلت على
quite the haul from night fishing today.
لقد كان صيدًا كبيرًا من الصيد الليلي اليوم.
Those willing may bite the hook.
يمكن لأولئك الراغبين أن يعضوا على الخطاف.
Have a seat.
خذ مقعدا.
You're full of youthful spirit.
أنت مليء بروح الشباب.
If I'm not mistaken,
إذا لم أكن مخطئا،
you must be Lord Wang Heng.
لا بد أنك اللورد وانغ هينج.
You know me?
أنت تعرفني؟
Lord Wang assists the Duke of Changyi
اللورد وانغ يساعد دوق تشانغي
and has achieved much.
وقد حقق الكثير.
Naturally, I've heard of your name.
بطبيعة الحال، لقد سمعت اسمك.
With such success at a young age,
مع هذا النجاح في سن مبكرة،
now coming to the capital,
الآن نأتي إلى العاصمة،
you must be aiming to achieve grand ambitions.
يجب أن يكون هدفك هو تحقيق طموحات كبيرة.
If things continue this way,
إذا استمرت الأمور على هذا النحو،
one day you may be appointed
قد يتم تعيينك يومًا ما
Grand General.
الجنرال الكبير.
May I ask your esteemed name?
هل يجوز لي أن أسأل عن اسمك الكريم؟
I am
أنا أكون
Huo Guang.
هوو قوانغ.
♪Watch the storm; hear the night rain fall♪
♪شاهد العاصفة؛ استمع إلى صوت هطول المطر في الليل♪
♪Till the light of dawn♪
♪حتى ضوء الفجر♪
♪A truth that cannot be spoken♪
♪حقيقة لا يمكن التحدث بها♪
♪Right and wrong matter♪
♪الصواب والخطأ مهمان♪
♪Yet I can't make the right choice♪
♪ولكن لا أستطيع اتخاذ الاختيار الصحيح♪
♪The lost player in the game♪
♪اللاعب الخاسر في اللعبة♪
♪Made a move by a twist of fate♪
♪لقد اتخذت خطوة بسبب تقلب القدر♪
♪The way back is lost, leaving nowhere to return♪
♪لقد ضاع طريق العودة، ولم يبق مكان للعودة♪
♪Borrow the endless cycles♪
♪استعارة الدورات التي لا نهاية لها♪
♪To fight for the most perfect outcome♪
♪القتال من أجل الحصول على النتيجة الأكثر مثالية♪
♪How to trace the threads and follow cause and effect♪
♪كيفية تتبع الخيوط واتباع السبب والنتيجة♪
♪Seeking a strategy without flaw♪
♪البحث عن استراتيجية خالية من العيوب♪
♪How to break free from this fated yet unforeseen lock♪
♪كيفية التحرر من هذا القفل المقدر وغير المتوقع♪
♪To live so as to shake the world♪
♪العيش من أجل هز العالم♪
♪With this journey, I gain a fiercer edge♪
♪مع هذه الرحلة، اكتسبت حافة أكثر شراسة♪
♪I've planned before I act countless times♪
♪لقد خططت قبل أن أتصرف مرات لا تحصى♪
♪Fatal danger turned into a jest♪
♪خطر قاتل تحول إلى مزحة♪
♪Through this road, I watch the endless rise and fall♪
♪من خلال هذا الطريق، أشاهد الصعود والهبوط الذي لا نهاية له♪
♪In the chapters lie ages of decay and bloom♪
♪في الفصول تكمن عصور من الاضمحلال والازدهار♪
♪Let us meet again♪
♪دعونا نلتقي مرة أخرى♪
♪One hurried path, and one at ease♪
♪مسار واحد سريع، ومسار آخر مريح♪